REACH ME



winona@winonaso.com www.winonaso.com www.winsemporium.etsy.com 519-502-7769

HELLO

I'm a graphic designer who focuses on the human experience.

My favourite tools include Adobe Photoshop and InDesign.

I have experience in creating user story-driven workflows, mockup-prototypes, and user interfaces. I also have experience in design documentation, and the proofing and editing of technical and published documents.

Toronto, ON

EDUCATION

MASTER OF DIGITAL MEDIA, Ryerson University

September 2016 - August 2017

Masters Thesis - AvatarMe: Digital Avatars in a Theme Park Queue Creating a Better Experience and an Emotional Connection

Graduate Assistant for Creativity and Collaboration (CRI 810)

Teaching Assistant for Digital Skills and Innovation for the Global Economy (EID 100)

Teaching Assistant/Graduate Assistant Program - Learning and Teaching Office

Overall GPA: 4.24

Ryerson Graduate Fellowship Scholarship

BACHELOR OF ARTS, University of Waterloo

September 2010 - December 2014

Major in Honours English - Rhetoric & Professional Writing, specializing in Digital Arts Communication

Arts & Business Co-op Program

Overall GPA: 3.3

University of Waterloo Merit Scholarship

2014-2015 - Rhetoric and Digital Design Award

WORK EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, Lord Cultural Resources

October 2017 - Present

Design and create assets for global clients based in the heritage and cultural industry

Create bids and templates in order to win contracts from potential clients

DIGITAL PRODUCTION ASSISTANT, Center for Extended Learning April 2015 - April 2016

April 2010 April 2010

Develop lecture slides and materials for University of Waterloo online courses

Collaborated with professors, other production assistants, developers in designing and publishing course content

Created illustrations and icons for online courses

DIGITAL CONTENT MANAGEMENT (CO-OP), Second Funnel

September 2013 - August 2014

Assisted VP of Customers with producing screen mock-ups, and presentation materials for client campaigns

Created digital assets for advertising campaigns for Gap, Nasty Gal, and Roots

UI/UX DESIGNER (CO-OP), Sony Entertainment Network

May 2013 - August 2013

September 2012 - December 2012

Produced user interface sketches, mock-ups, workflows, and prototypes

Created icons, graphics, and new features for Media Go software and website

Wrote design specification documentation for developers and stakeholders

STAFF, Imprint Publications

September 2010 - December 2014

Roles included Graphics Editor, Assistant Design Editor, Social Media Editor, Science & Technology Assistant, and 2014 Misprint Editor, and proofreader

Managed teams of designers, reporters, and volunteers to meet weekly publication deadlines

Layout of pages in university newspaper with attention to design and visual appeal

TALK TO YOU SOON!